supersimplelearning.com 2019-06-05

# Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions - Super Simple

Super Simple Online (the “Site”) takes the privacy of its users very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes what information is collected, and how it is used, when you visit the Site.

### Personal Information

The only personal information we collect is what you have provided. If you leave a comment, email us, submit a request via our [Support Page](https://support.supersimple.com/), or interact with us on social media, you are electing to give us personally-identifiable information such as your name, email address, geographic location, or other information which could be used to locate or contact you. We will never sell or solicit your personal information to a third-party and we endeavour to store your details in confidence.

### Submissions

Occasionally the Site will ask its audience for participation via online submissions of media including but not limited to children’s artwork, family photographs, video clips, general geographic locations, etc through the Site, social media platforms, or email. These submissions will only be accepted by persons over the age of eighteen. Submissions from minors will only be accepted via the legal parent or guardian and the submitter agrees that the submissions are free of copyrights and are suitable for sharing on the Site and all of its related platforms. All submissions will become property of Super Simple Online, and the submitter agrees that the media can be used for any purpose including on the Site, on social media, in advertising, etc.

### Unsolicited Submissions

The Site does not condone unsolicited submissions of any media including but not limited to artwork, songs, song lyrics, show ideas, video and audio clips. All submissions will become property of Super Simple Online, and the submitter agrees that the media can be used for any purpose including on the Site, on social media, in advertising, etc.

### Non-Personal Information

Our website host, advertising network, advertisers, and affiliates (“Affiliates”) collect non-personal information such as your IP address, the type of browser you are using, the referring website, the operating system you are using, your Internet service provider, the search terms you use on our Site, the specific web pages you visit, and the duration of your visits.

### Cookies

An HTTP cookie (also called web cookie, internet cookie, browser cookie, or simply cookie) is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored on the user’s computer by the user’s web browser while the user is browsing. Cookies are designed to be a reliable mechanism for websites to remember stateful information (such as items added in the shopping cart in an online store) or to record the user’s browsing activity (including clicking particular buttons, logging in, or recording which pages were visited in the past). The Site does not use cookies, but one or more of our Affiliates do (such as our [Shop](https://shop.supersimpleonline.com/10121116/policies/8337221.html)) and their use of cookies is governed by their own privacy policies.

### Information Use

Our Affiliates may use non-personal information to help analyze site traffic, understand customer needs and trends, and carry out targeted promotional activities. They may use non-personal information by itself or aggregate it with information they have obtained from others to produce research reports and other information and data, and may share such information with third parties.

### Third-Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on the Site. Those companies may use non-personal information about your visit to the Site to display ads for goods and services which may be of interest to you.

### Links to Other Sites

We provide links to other websites, and we are not responsible for the content or information use on any of those sites. You should review each site’s privacy policy.

### Modification

We will amend or revise this Privacy Policy from time to time and recommend you review it periodically. If you continue to view the Site after revisions to this policy have been made, you are automatically agreeing to the new terms.

### Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our Terms & Conditions, please contact us.

    _Last Updated January 29th, 2018_
